<resources>
    <string name="app_name">exer2_lorente_B9L</string>
    <string name="title">Which Starter Are You?</string>
    <string name="charmander_des">
        The flame that burns at the tip of its tail is an indication of its emotions.
        The flame wavers when Charmander is enjoying itself. If the Pokémon becomes
        enraged, the flame burns fiercely.

        Charmander is a bipedal, reptilian Pokémon with a primarily orange body and blue eyes.
        Its underside from the chest down and the soles of its feet are cream-colored. It has
        two small fangs visible in its upper jaw and two smaller fangs in its lower jaw. A fire
        burns at the tip of this Pokémon\'s slender tail and has blazed there since Charmander\'s
        birth. The flame can be used as an indication of Charmander\'s health and mood, burning
        brightly when the Pokémon is strong, weakly when it is exhausted, wavering when it is
        happy, and blazing when it is enraged. It is said that Charmander dies if its flame goes
        out. However, if the Pokémon is healthy, the flame will continue to burn even if it gets
        a bit wet and is said to steam in the rain.
    </string>

    <string name="bulbasaur_des">
        Bulbasaur can be seen napping in bright sunlight. There is a seed on its back.
        By soaking up the sun’s rays, the seed grows progressively larger.

        Bulbasaur is a small, quadruped Pokémon that has blue-green skin with darker patches.
        It has red eyes with white pupils, pointed, ear-like structures on top of its head, and
        a short, blunt snout with a wide mouth. A pair of small, pointed teeth are visible in the
        upper jaw when its mouth is open. Each of its thick legs ends with three sharp claws. On
        its back is a green plant bulb, which is grown from a seed planted there at birth. The bulb
        provides it with energy through photosynthesis as well as from the nutrient-rich seeds
        contained within.
    </string>

    <string name = "squirtle_des">
        Squirtle’s shell is not merely used for protection. The shell’s rounded shape
        and the grooves on its surface help minimize resistance in water, enabling this
        Pokémon to swim at high speeds.

        Squirtle\'s shell is a useful tool. It can withdraw into the shell for protection or to sleep.
        The grooved, rounded shape helps to reduce water resistance, allowing the Pokémon to swim at
        high speeds. Squirtle can spray foamy water from its mouth with great accuracy. Squirtle is
        scarce in the wild, although it can be found around small ponds and lakes. The anime has shown
        that it can be found living on secluded islands with other members of its evolutionary line.
        In the past, Skull Bash was its signature move.
    </string>

    <string name="cyndaquil_des">
        Cyndaquil protects itself by flaring up the flames on its back. The flames are
        vigorous if the Pokémon is angry. However, if it is tired, the flames splutter
        fitfully with incomplete combustion.

        Cyndaquil is a small, bipedal Pokémon with bluish fur on top of its body and cream-colored fur
        on its underside. Its eyes are usually seen closed, and it has a long, thin snout. Its arms are
        short, but its legs are slightly more developed and have a single nail on each foot. On its back
        are four red circles that can erupt into flames. When the flames are burning, its back seems to
        be covered in spines.
    </string>

    <string name="chikorita_des">
        In battle, Chikorita waves its leaf around to keep the foe at bay. However, a
        sweet fragrance also wafts from the leaf, becalming the battling Pokémon and
        creating a cozy, friendly atmosphere all around.

        Chikorita is a small, pale green Pokémon with dark green buds around its neck. Its head is large
        in proportion to the rest of its body, and it has big red eyes. It has four short legs with a single
        nailed toe on each and a stubby tail. On top of its head is a large, green leaf that is usually longer
        than its body. A soothing aroma wafts from the leaf, which can calm battling Pokémon.
    </string>

    <string name="totodile_des">
        Despite the smallness of its body, Totodile’s jaws are very powerful. While
        the Pokémon may think it is just playfully nipping, its bite has enough
        power to cause serious injury.

        Totodile is a bipedal, crocodilian Pokémon with well-developed jaws. It has red eyes with ridges above them,
        black markings around its eyes, and several sharp teeth. On its chest is a yellow, V-shaped marking that extends
        to its arms; there is a thin line through the center of the marking. Totodile has five fingers and three toes.
        Down its back is a row of three red spines with a small, red ridge on either side. The tip of its tail has a
        single red spine as well. Totodile tends to be playful by nature and has a habit of biting anything it sees,
        including its Trainer.
    </string>

    <string name="popplio_des">
        This Pokémon snorts body fluids from its nose, blowing balloons to smash into its
        foes. It’s famous for being a hard worker.

        Popplio is a pinniped Pokémon that is primarily blue. It has large eyes, a long, white snout with black whiskers,
        and round, pink nose. There is a small, rounded earflap on each side of its head. Around its neck is a light blue
        ruff, which extends past its shoulders. It has four flippers. The front flippers are larger than the hind, and have
        white markings separating its toes.

    </string>

    <string name="treecko_des">
        Treecko is cool, calm, and collected—it never panics under any situation. If a bigger
        foe were to glare at this Pokémon, it would glare right back without conceding an
        inch of ground.

        Treecko is a small, green, bipedal reptilian Pokémon. It has yellow eyes with long, narrow pupils. Treecko\'s hands and
        feet each have three digits covered with tiny spikes. These spikes allow it to scale vertical walls with ease. Its stomach
        and throat are red. It also has a line across on its stomach resembling a pouch. Treecko has a large, dark green tail with
        two separate lobes that it uses to sense humidity.

    </string>

    <string name="torchic_des">
        Torchic sticks with its Trainer, following behind with unsteady steps. This Pokémon
        breathes fire of over 1,800 degrees Fahrenheit, including fireballs that leave the
        foe scorched black.

        Torchic is a small, chick Pokémon with stubby, downy, yellow wings. Its body is covered
        with orange feathers. There is an orange and yellow crest on its head that resembles a
        flame. Its two thin legs and short beak of are a light brownish yellow, and the feet have
        three toes in front and one in the back. A male Torchic will have a small black speck on
        its rear that is not present in females.
    </string>


    <string name="piplup_des">
        Piplup is a light-blue, penguin-like Pokémon, which is covered in thick down to insulate against the cold.
        It has a dark blue head with a primarily white face and a short, yellow beak. The dark blue feathers on its
        head extend down its back and around its neck, which causes it to appear to be wearing a cape.

        Because it is very proud, it hates accepting food from people. Its thick down
        guards it from cold.
    </string>


    <string name="none">

    </string>
</resources>
